Garroe Wah

1191 S 900 W, Salt Lake City, UT 84104 (801) 444-8384 | garroewah@gmail.com

Career Summary

Over 7 years of experience working with the programs and services of the Department of Workforce Services. This includes working with customers in person and over the phone. Most recently, I worked as a Community Resource Specialist for Refugee Services Office (RSO), DWS. My overall experience includes working with individuals from diverse backgrounds and cultures to identify needs, provide direct services, and make referrals to community program and resources.

Skills

- Strong communication
- Customer Service (In person/over the phone)
- Uwork, eRep, Content Manager
- Problem Solving

- Data Entry
- DWS Policy / Procedure
- File Management
- Case Management

Professional Work Experience

University of Utah - U of U

Community Liaison (Thai – Burma Border)

February 2018 – August 2018

- Developed and conducted culture orientation class to U of U students and professors
- Involved in community empowerment strategy planning meetings with U of U students and professors for the trip to Thai-Burma refugee camps.
- Conducted Community Capacity Building training to the health workers, youth and camp leaders in two refugee camps on Thai border.

Department of Workforce Services

July 2014 – August 2017

Community Resource Specialist

- Assisted customers coming in to the Refugee Training and Education Center
- Connected clients to appropriate resources to meet their needs
- Created and developed programs serving refugee communities such as Citizenship, Driver License and Basic Computer classes serving hundreds of clients
- Provided around the clock support and problem solving for families in crisis
- Performed data entry in detail daily so that families' needs and progress are tracked
- Meet with community partners frequently to determine needs in the community.

Department of Workforce Services-DWS

September 2009 – June 2014

Employment Counselor

- Registered refugees to DWS assistance programs including TANF, Food Stamps, and Job Readiness Training.
- Initiated need assessment and assigned customers to job readiness training, English class and/or community services
- Case managed forty plus families from diverse cultures concurrently.
- Met and built good relationship with employers and referred refugees that are work ready
- Lead case staffing meetings to brainstorming and problem solving issues with supervisor and Licensed Clinic Therapists.
- Performed data entry utilizing Content Management systems such as Uworks, eRep,
 eShare for case registration, benefit issuances and communication

Education

Umphium High School, Thailand High School Diploma 2003

Special Education Program (SEP), Thailand

2003 - 2005

Certificate of Graduation

- Studied general subjects: Math, Science, English, Geology
- Critical thinking and problem-solving projects

Salt Lake Community College

2016 - Present

Working on Associate Degree

- Currently working on the required college general courses
- Pursuing major in Computer Science

Garroe Wah

1170 Jeremy Street, Salt Lake City, UT 84104 (801) 865-5270 | garroewah@gmail.com

Professional References

Dr. Rosemarie Hunter

Associate Professor
College of Social Work
University of Utah
(801) 589-6485
R.Hunter@socwk.utah.edu

Michael Pekarske

Supervisor Community Resource Specialist Team Refugee Services Office, DWS (801) 989-7808 mpekarske@utah.gov

Mario Kljajo

Manager Refugee Services Office, DWS (385) 272-6211 mkljajo@utah.gov